// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Planet which is small in our Solar System?",
    answer: "Mercury",
    options: [
      "Uranus",
      "Jupiter",
      "Earth",
      "Mercury"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Planet which has only one Moon in its Orbit?",
    answer: "Earth",
    options: [
      "Venus",
      "Earth",
      "Jupiter",
      "Mars"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Planet which is Nearest to the Sun?",
    answer: "Mercury",
    options: [
      "Saturn",
      "Mars",
      "Mercury",
      "Uranus"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "How many Planets are there in our Solar System?",
    answer: "8",
    options: [
      "8",
      "6",
      "9",
      "4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Who is the First Female Astronaut from India?",
    answer: "Kalpana chawla",
    options: [
      "Sunita williams",
      "Kalpana chawla",
      "Lisa norwak",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "If an Astronaut goes in Space he/she will Observe the Sky as?",
    answer: "Black",
    options: [
      "White",
      "Red",
      "Blue",
      "Black"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Planets which have no Moon?",
    answer: "Mercury And Venus",
    options: [
      "Pluto And Mercury",
      "Mars And Venus",
      "Mercury And Venus",
      "Pluto And Mars"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The Coldest Planet in our Solar System?",
    answer: "Uranus",
    options: [
      "Pluto",
      "Uranus",
      "Venus",
      "Jupiter"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Planet which Lies at the Outermost Orbit of the Solar System?",
    answer: "Neptune",
    options: [
      "Neptune",
      "Saturn",
      "Uranus",
      "Mercury"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is not a Gas Planet?",
    answer: "Venus",
    options: [
      "Jupiter",
      "Uranus",
      "Neptune",
      "Venus"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "How long is One Year on Jupiter?",
    answer: "12 Earth years",
    options: [
      "11 Earth years",
      "17 Earth years",
      "12 Earth years",
      "20 Earth years"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Which is the Oldest Planet in our Solar System?",
    answer: "Jupiter",
    options: [
      "Jupiter",
      "Mars",
      "Earth",
      "Mercury"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Which Planet Spins Backward Relative to the others?",
    answer: "Venus",
    options: [
      "Earth",
      "Venus",
      "Neptune",
      "Mars"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which Planet has the Fastest Rotation?",
    answer: "Jupiter",
    options: [
      "Mercury",
      "Mars",
      "Venus",
      "Jupiter"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Planet which is Called as the Red Planet?",
    answer: "Mars",
    options: [
      "Sun",
      "Moon",
      "Mars",
      "Saturn"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Unscramble the Word 'ARTHE'.",
    answer: "EARTH",
    options: [
      "ERATH",
      "EARTH",
      "HTRAE",
      "RHTEA"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Unscramble the Word 'MONO'.",
    answer: "MOON",
    options: [
      "MOON",
      "NOOM",
      "NOMO",
      "OONM"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Unscramble the Word 'SNUVE'.",
    answer: "VENUS",
    options: [
      "SUNEV",
      "VSNUE",
      "VENUS",
      "UNSVE"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Unscramble the Word 'ARMS'.",
    answer: "MARS",
    options: [
      "SRAM",
      "AMRS",
      "MASR",
      "MARS"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Unscramble the Word 'PSECA'.",
    answer: "SPACE",
    options: [
      "ECAPS",
      "SPACE",
      "ACPSE",
      "ESPAC"
    ]
  },
];